Finding Aid for Philip A. Hart Papers
Bentley Historical Library
- Sound recordings
  - Reel-to-reel (7 in.)
    - 1961 (Box 268)
      - Sleeping Bear National Park Meeting at Glen Lake, MI, part 2, August 30, 1961; 3 3/4 ips; poor recording (Box 268)
        (tape no.7)
      - Sleeping Bear National Park questions and answers with Senator Hart, 1961 November 11; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 268)
        - [Part 1], [85193-SR-8-1]; (Hart answers questions about Sleeping Bear National Park and the bill to protect Sleeping Bear Sand Dunes. Content ends at 13:30, remainder of tape is a music recording.)
      - Senator Philip Hart at the Detroit Press Club, 1961 November 01; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 268)
        - [Part 1], [85193-SR-9-1]; (Hart talks about Sleeping Bear Dunes; also speaks about his trip to Africa, and problems it is facing in a post-colonial era.)
      - Voice of America, Les Higbie interview with Senator Phillip Hart., 1961 November 01; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 268)
        - [Part 1], [85193-SR-10-1]; (Philip Hart, discusses his trip to 15 countries in Africa including Congo, Angola, and post-colonial African politics.)
    - 1962
      - "Opinion" program with Sen. Philip A. Hart speaking about immigration issues, politics, and Michigan's gubernatorial race, October 1, 1962 (Box 268)
        (tape no. 11)
      - Blank (Box 268)
        (tape no. 12)
    - 1964
      - "Leading Question" radio program with Philip A. Hart and Senator Herman Talmadge of Georgia debating the Civil Rights Bill., 1964 March 31; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 268)
        - [Part 1], [85193-SR-13-1]; (Debate between Hart, a supporter of the Civil Rights Bill, and Talmadge, an opponent of the Civil Rights Bill.)
      - Michigan Chamber of Commerce conference. Philip A. Hart, moderator, 1964 April 21; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 268)
        - [Part 1], [85193-SR-14-1]; (Tape 1; Recording of a conference on land use and planning; open space planning; urban renewal.)
      - Michigan Chamber of Commerce conference. Philip A. Hart, moderator, 1964 April 21; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 268)
        - [Part 1], [85193-SR-15-1]; (Tape 2; Recording of a conference on Area Redevelopment Act; Manpower Development and Training Act.)
      - Michigan Chamber of Commerce conference. Philip A. Hart, moderator, 1964 April 21; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 268)
        - [Part 1], [85193-SR-16-1]; (Tape 3; Recording of a conference on Economic Opportunity Act (McNamara Bill); War on Poverty.)
      - Michigan Chamber of Commerce conference. Philip A. Hart, moderator, 1964 April 21; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 268)
        - [Part 1], [85193-SR-17-1]; (Tape 4; Recording of a conference on War on Poverty (cont. from tape 3), Budget, Economic Opportunity Act.)
      - 16th Anniversary of Israel Statehood; Tribute to Hart, May 24, 1964; 5 tapes (Box 268)
        (tapes nos. 18-22)
      - Democratic Spots, October 1964 (Box 268)
        (tape no. 23)
    - 1965
      - Truth in Packaging, Medicare, Sleeping Bear Dunes discussed, January 14, 1965 (Box 268)
        (tape no. 24)
      - "This is your business" program of the Michigan Chamber of Commerce regarding Truth in Packaging legislation, February 22, 1965 (Box 268)
        (tape no. 25)
      - WBBM "Conference Call" program with PAH discussing Truth in Packaging, July 1965 (Box 268)
        (tape no. 26)
    - 1969
      - Michigan State University speeches with Donald Riegle, Hart, and acting MSU President Walter Adams discussing the war in Vietnam, October 15, 1969; 3 3/4 ips (Box 268)
        (tape no. 27)
    - 1970
      - "Earth Day: Fight for a Better Environment" report, April 26, 1970 (Box 268)
        (tape no. 28)
      - Babe Ruth Baseball Breakfast, June 16, 1970 (Box 268)
        (tape no. 29)
    - 1973
      - Excerpts from "For What It's Worth" WRIF-Detroit, October 21, 1973; 1 7/8 ips (Box 268)
        (tape no. 30)
    - 1976
      - National Board of the Leadership Conference on Civil Rights Dinner saluting Senator Hart, January 26, 1976; 3 3/4 ips (Box 268)
        (tape no. 31; continued on tape 93)
      - Dedication ceremony of Phil Hart Visitor Center at Sleeping Bear Dunes National Lakeshore, 1976 December 10; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 268)
        - [Part 1], [85193-SR-32-1]; (Phil Hart speaking about the importance of environmental protection at Sleeping Bear Dunes Dedication event.)
        - [Part 2], [85193-SR-32-2]; mp3 file; (Phil Hart speaking about the importance of environmental protection at Sleeping Bear Dunes Dedication event.)
    - Undated
      - Michigan Mayor's Conference, 5 tapes
        - Tape #1, Introduction by Sen. Hart, Kermit Gordon, James Quigley, Arvin Basnight (Box 268)
          (tape no.33)
        - Tape #2, Rex Whitton, Wm. Cassidy, Jack T. Conway, Wm. Slayton (Box 268)
          (tape no.34)
        - Tape #3, Abner D. Silverman, Sen. Hart, Richard Webb, Charles Gasque, Ben Thompson (Box 268)
        - Tape #4, Ben Thompson, John Horn, Mr. Fine, Mr. Brown, John Baker, Bill Batt (Box 268)
          (tape no. 36)
        - Tape #5, Bill Batt, Mr. Sidney Woolner (Box 268)
          (tape no. 37)
      - Sleeping Bear Dunes Comments, Radio Station WCCW, Traverse City (Box 269)
        (tape no. 38)
      - (probable) Cobo Hall dinner honoring Senator Hart, 1970; 3 3/4 ips (Box 269)
        (tape no. 39)
      - POW interviews with Jane Hart in Hanoi (Box 269)
        (tape no. 40)
      - 8/25 Capitol Cloakroom, DUB (part 1) (Box 269)
        (tape no. 41)
      - 8/25 Capitol Cloakroom, DUB (part 2) (Box 269)
        (tape no. 42)
      - Tape no. 43 eliminated during the reprocessing, 2007 (Box 269)
  - Reel-to-reel tapes (5 in.)
    - 1959
      - Radio program with PAH discussing Michigan's agricultural economy and price supports, February 1959 (Box 269)
        (tape no. 44)
      - Tape no. 45 eliminated during the 2007 reprocessing (Box 269)
      - April 10, 1959; May 11, 1959 mainly blank (Box 269)
        (tape no. 46)
      - March 19, 1959; April 30, 1959 Senator Patrick McNamara speaking from Washington on the St. Lawrence Seaway (Box 269)
        (tape no. 47)
      - Sen. Hart Answers Questions from Michigan Citizens, October 20, 1959; 3 cuts, each approx. 4 min. (Box 269)
        (includes script)
        (tape no. 48)
    - 1960
      (taped radio spots, 4 or 5 topics, each approx. 1 min., script available)
      - ; Topics: Civil Rights, Drug Price Hearings, School Construction, Goldwater's Report, Farm legislation, February 19, 1960 (Box 269)
        (tape no. 49)
      - ; Topics: Civil Rights, Water Pollution, Wheat Legislation, Home Gardening, Agriculture booklets, March 4, 1960 (Box 269)
        (tape no. 50)
    - 1961
      (taped radio spots (except for tapes 58-59), 4 or 5 topics, each approx. 1 min., script available)
      - ; Topics: Civil Rights, New Jobs, Servicemen, Inaugural, School milk program, January 24, 1961 (Box 269)
        (tape no. 51)
      - ; Topics: Refugees, Rules Committee fight, State of the Union, James Landis, Water, February 4, 1961 (Box 269)
        (tape no.52)
      - ; Topics: Robert C. Weaver appointment, Unemployment, New Frontier weather, Farmland, Feed Grain Task Force, February 20, 1961 (Box 269)
        (tape no. 53)
      - ; Topics: Federal Aid to Education, Highway Program, Peace Corps, Feed Grain Program, G. Mennen Williams in Africa, March 6, 1961 (Box 269)
        (tape no. 54)
      - ; Topics: President Kennedy's Housing Message, Small business firms, Aid to Dependent Children, JFK's message on Agriculture, Depressed Areas, March 9, 1961 (Box 269)
        (tape no. 55)
      - ; Topics: Michigan Mayors Visit, Adrian, Feed Grain Bill, Price Supports, Cherry Blossoms, April 4, 1961 (Box 269)
        (tape no. 56)
      - ; Topics: St. Lawrence Seaway, Clark Bill, Soviet Man Launch, Consumer hearings, Agriculture, April 18, 1961 (Box 269)
        (tape no. 57)
      - "Capital Report" WWJ radio program with Philip A. Hart, 1961 May 03-04; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 5 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 269)
        - [Part 1], [85193-SR-58-1]; (Philip A. Hart discussing the economic impact of national defense spending.)
      - Discussion between Philip A. Hart and Congressman John Blatnik of Minnesota, 1961 May 08; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 5 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 269)
        - [Part 1], [85193-SR-59-1]; (Discussion on topic of water pollution control legislation.)
      - ; Topics: Mayors Conference, Attorney General Kennedy, National Forests, Economic Impact of National Defense, Adrian, May 9, 1961 (Box 269)
        (tape no. 60)
      - ; Topics: Clark Bill, Alabama Riots, Education, New Furniture, May 24, 1961 (Box 269)
        (tape no. 61)
      - ; Topics: Anti-Trust Committee Hearings, Summit Meeting, School Segregation Case, University of Michigan Band, Crime Packages, June 8, 1961 (Box 269)
        (tape no. 62)
      - ; Topics: Highway Program, Detroit Tigers, Consumer Hearings, Water Pollution, Mexican Labor, June 23, 1961 (Box 269)
        (tape no. 63)
      - ; Topics: Consumers, National Parks, Weather Bureau Service, Small Business Amendment, Social Security, Housing Bill -- Community Facilities, Reorganization of FCC, July 5, 1961 (Box 269)
        (tape no. 64)
      - ; Topics: Refugees, National Parks, Wheat, Apples and Cherries, Consumer Hearings, July 19, 1961 (Box 269)
        (tape no. 65)
      - ; Topics: Civil Rights Commission, Area Redevelopment, Foreign Aid, Truth in Lending, August 1, 1961 (Box 269)
        (tape no. 66)
      - ; Topics: Hijackers, Foreign Aid, Professional Sports, Food and Drug Actions, August 17, 1961 (Box 269)
        (tape no. 67)
      - ; Topics: Manpower Retraining, Machrowicz Judgeship, Civil Rights Rules Fight, Visit with President Kennedy and Nairo Group, Aid to Education Bill, August 29, 1961 (Box 269)
        (tape no. 68)
      - ; Topics: Civil Rights Commission Report, Aid to Education, Cloture, Nuclear Testing, Watershed Projects, September 12, 1961 (Box 269)
        (tape no. 69)
    - 1962
      (taped radio spots (except for tape 82), 4 or 5 topics, each approx. 1 min., script available)
      - ; Topics: Congress, Africa, Reciprocal Trade, Farm Program, January 17, 1962 (Box 269)
        (tape no. 70)
      - ; Topics: Summit Conference, Packaging and Labeling, College Facilities, Open Space, February 19, 1962 (Box 269)
        (tape no. 71)
      - ; Topics: John H. Glenn, Jr., Packaging Hearings, O.T.A.C., Agriculture, Medical Care, Peace, Forestry, March 1, 1962 (Box 269)
        (tape no. 72)
      - ; Topics: UN Bond Issue, Wiretapping, Recreation, Packaging Hearings, April 12, 1962 (Box 269)
        (tape no. 73)
      - ; Topics: Farm Bill, Literacy Tests, Steel Prices, Sleeping Bear Dunes, April 27, 1962 (Box 270)
        (tape no. 74)
      - ; Topics: National Guard Reorganization, Frederick Douglass Memorial, Young American Medal Winners, Health Insurance through Social Security, Farm Program, May 28, 1962 (Box 270)
        (tape no. 75)
      - Tape no. 76 eliminated during the 2007 reprocessing (Box 270)
      - ; Topics: Packaging, Public Works, Refugees, Pictured Rocks, June 11, 1962 (Box 270)
        (tape no. 77)
      - ; Topics: Sleeping Bear Dunes, Federal Tax Cut, Wheat Legislation, Personal Diplomacy (Mexico), Health Insurance, July 10, 1962 (Box 270)
        (tape no. 78)
      - ; Topics: School Lunch Program, Frederick Douglass Memorial, Thurgood Marshall, Military Authorization Bill, July 24, 1962 (Box 270)
        (tape no. 79)
      - ; Topics: Drug Bill, Food Stamp Program, Economic Impact of National Defense, Six Percent Differential, August 1, 1962 (Box 270)
        (tape no. 80)
      - ; Topics: National School Lunch Program, Small Business, Test Ban Treaty, Drug Bill, August 17, 1962 (Box 270)
        (tape no. 81)
      - President Kennedy's Address at the Muskegon, Airport, 1962 October 06; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 5 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 270)
        - [Part 1], [85193-SR-82-1]; (Kennedy address during 1962 House of Representatives elections.)
      - ; Topics: Public works and job creation, truth in packaging, Congo, Cuban refugees, legislative objectives of Congress, December 19, 1962 (Box 270)
        (tape no. 83)
    - 1974
      - Press Conference, February 12, 1974; 1 7 /8 ips (Box 270)
        (tape no. 84)
      - Press Conference, April 29, 1974; 1 7 /8 ips (Box 270)
        (tape no. 85)
      - Hart News conference and briefing, June-July 1974; 1 7 /8 ips (Box 270)
        (tape no. 86)
      - Press Conference, December 19, 1974; 1 7 /8 ips (Box 270)
        (tape no. 87)
      - Press Conference, December 19, 1974; 1 7 /8 ips (Box 270)
        (tape no. 88)
    - 1975
      - Press Conferences, January 16, 1975-February 13, 1975; 1 7 /8 ips (Box 270)
        (tape no. 89)
      - ; Monday Staff Meeting, legislation discussion, March 4, 1975; 1 7 /8 ips (Box 270)
        (tape no.90)
      - ; Retirement Announcement, Beeper Call, Press Conference, June 5-June 19, 1975; 1 7 /8 ips (Box 270)
        (tape no. 91)
      - ; Press Conferences, Joe Mc Caffrey, July 10, 1975-October 16, 1975; 1 7 /8 ips (Box 270)
        (tape no. 92)
    - 1976
      - ; National Board of the Leadership Conference on Civil Rights Dinner: Sen. Hart, Mr. Wilkens, Rabbi David Saperstein, "You Gotta Have Hart", January 26, 1976; 3 3/4 ips (Box 270)
        (tape no.93; continued from tape 31)
      - News Conference, February 27, 1976; 1 7 /8 ips (Box 270)
        (tape no. 94)
      - [Philip A. Hart - ] Last Press Conference, 1976 July 01; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 5 inch, 1 7 /8 ips (Box 270)
        - [Part 1], [85193-SR-95-1]; (Hart discusses Sleeping Bear Dunes National Lakeshore, upcoming elections, and retirement.)
      - [Philip A. Hart - ] Last Press Conference, 1976 July 01; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 5 inch, 1 7 /8 ips (Box 270)
        - [Part 1], [85193-SR-95-1]; (Hart discusses Sleeping Bear Dunes National Lakeshore, upcoming elections, and retirement.)
    - Hart's Last Speech other remarks, and Jane Hart's interview with John Chambers, WWJ-TV, 1976 September 26, 1976 December 02; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 5 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 270)
      - [Part 1], [85193-SR-96-1]; (Hart's Last Speech September 29, 1976, other remarks, and Jane Hart's interview with John Chambers, WWJ-TV December 2, 1976; Hart's speech concludes at 35:29, Jane Hart's interview begins at 35:30.)
    - Undated
      - (probable date); "Report to People" Storer Broadcasting Co. program with PAH discussing Truth in Packaging legislation, March 14, 1966; 13:40 min. (Box 270)
        (tape no. 97)
      - Tape no. 98 eliminated during the 2007 reprocessing (Box 270)
      - 1970; "The Worker's Stake in the 1970 Elections, George Meany, Pres. AFL-CIO (Box 270)
        (tape no. 99)
      - Tapes no. 100-101 eliminated during the 2007 reprocessing (Box 270)
      - ; Newsmag (Canadian Program) interview with Herbert Marcuse re student protests, Undated (Box 270)
        (tape no. 102)
      - July 26 Transcripts on PAH Remarks on Prayer Amendments (Box 270)
        (tape no. 103)
      - Jane Hart's press conference following her conviction, 1969; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 5 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 270)
        - [Tape 1, Part 1], [85193-SR-104-1]; (Tape 1; Jane Hart discusses her arrest and conviction for participation in an antiwar demonstration.)
        - [Tape 2, Part 1], [85193-SR-105-1]; (Tape 2; Jane Hart discusses her arrest and conviction for participation in an antiwar demonstration.)
      - Four radio spots, various issues, July 21, 1964 (Box 271)
        (tape no. 106)
      - Area Redevelopment Program, PAH with Hal Davis, October 5, 1964; 4:29 min. (Box 271)
        (tape no. 107)
      - Tapes no. 108-112 eliminated during the 2007 reprocessing (Box 271)
      - PAH discusses the sending of troops into Cambodia, June 12, 1970 (Box 271)
        (tape no. 113)
      - ; Promo for Democratic dinner, October 12, 1973; 2:15 min. (Box 271)
        (tape no. 114)
      - Tape no. 115 eliminated during the 2007 reprocessing (Box 271)
  - Reel-to-Reel tapes (3 in, 3-inch, brief spots, under 60 sec. each; 7 1/2 ips
    - August 24, 1967 (Box 271)
      (highways, scenic highways)
      (tape no. 116)
    - January 27, 1970 (Box 271)
      (American Indian issues)
      (tape no. 117)
    - Tape no. 118 eliminated during the 2007 reprocessing (Box 271)
    - April 28, 1970 (Box 271)
      (power shortages, price increases)
      (tape no. 119)
    - Tapes no. 120-124 eliminated during the 2007 reprocessing (Box 271)
    - June 9, 1970 (Box 271)
      (domestic issues)
      (tape no. 125)
    - Tapes no. 126-127 eliminated during the 2007 reprocessing (Box 271)
    - August 12, 1970 (Box 271)
      (SALT talks)
      (tape no. 128)
    - Tape no. 129 eliminated during the 2007 reprocessing (Box 271)
    - ; Sleeping Bear Dunes, September 29, 1970 (Box 271)
      (tape no. 130)
    - Tape no. 131 eliminated during the 2007 reprocessing (Box 271)
    - ; Veto of legislation regulating expenditures for political advertisements on television, October 12, 1970 (Box 271)
      (tape no. 132)
    - ; Vietnam War, January 20, 1972 (Box 271)
      (tape no. 133)
    - ; No-fault automobile insurance, May 26, 1972 (Box 271)
      (tape no. 134)
    - ; Criticism of Nixon's refusal to spend moneys appropriated by Congress for domestic programs, April 10, 1973 (Box 271)
      (tape no. 135)
  - Miscellaneous
    - PAH apologizes for not being able to break away from DC; mentions extending voting rights act, protecting right of dissent (Box 271)
      (tape no. 136)
    - Town meeting, with various speakers discussing effects of unemployment and plant closings; PAH responds (Box 271)
      (tape no. 137)
    - Members of Lansing Area Peace Council and other peace groups discuss Indo-China War and rise of US militarism; speak out criticizing PAH and others (Box 271)
      (tape no. 138)
    - Depressed areas bill, loans and grants to such areas (Box 271)
      (tape no. 139)
    - ; PAH gives commencement address to graduates of Eastern Michigan University on topic of Civil Rights, June 8, 1963 (Box 271)
      (tape no. 148)
    - Unidentified, 1 7/8 ips (Box 271)
      (tape no. 149)
  - Cassette tapes
    - Flint Jewish Community Council Award, September 28, 1978 (Box 271)
      (tape no. 150)
    - ; Senator Hart participating in town hall meeting discussing local Michigan issues, Undated (Box 271)
      (tape no. 151)
    - ; Conversations between Paul F. Sutphen of Owosso, MI first with PAH and latter with a Martha Griffiths staff member, Undated (Box 271)
      (tape no. 152)
- Visual Materials, 10 linear feet
  Visual Materials (10 linear ft.) consists of four subseries. There is about one linear foot of slides and photographs arranged by subject matter. In addition, this series includes one oversize folder of political cartoons given to Hart over the course of his career, nine linear feet of motion picture films (approximately 100 reels) with different subject matter, and a small videotape subseries. Some of the films have use copies as well as negative and sound reels. In addition to ten 2-inch video tapes, the Videotape subseries includes a videotape compilation of the film clips relating to the proposed Sleeping Bear Dunes National Lakeshore or Pictured Rock Lakeshore. This tape consists mainly of brief, 2-3 minute, "messages" filmed at the U.S. Senate television/film studio, but also several longer interviews. The first three segments on this tape are positive prints, the others are "lavender" negatives (a copy negative rather than original camera negative). The negative film was electronically converted to positive image on the videotape. All have optical sound on film.
  - Slides and photographs
    - Slides (Box 272)
    - Photonegatives (Box 272)
      (include portraits of PAH, family portraits, ca. 1965, etc)
      (folder no. 1)
    - Photographs- Topically arranged (Folder UAm)
      - African trip, October 1961 (Box 272)
        (folder no. 2)
      - Airline travel shots (Box 272)
        (folder no. 3)
      - Automobile promotion (Box 272)
        (folder no. 4)
      - Awards presented to others (Box 272)
        (folder no. 5)
      - Campaigns
        - 1950s (Box 272)
          (folder no. 7)
        - 1960 (Box 272)
          (folder no. 8)
        - Other (Box 272)
          (folder no. 9)
      - Capitol shots (interior) (Box 272)
        (folder no. 10)
      - Celebrities (Box 272)
        (folder no. 11)
      - Civil rights (Box 272)
        (folder no. 12)
      - Colleagues
        - Groups (Box 272)
          (folder no. 13)
        - Individuals (Box 272)
          (folder no. 14)
        - Michigan groups (Box 272)
          (folder no. 15)
        - Michigan individuals (Box 272)
          (folder no. 16)
      - Constituents
        - circa 1949-1960
          - Groups (Box 272)
            (folder no. 17)
          - Individuals (Box 272)
            (folder no. 18)
        - 1960-1976
          - Identified individuals (Box 272)
            (folder no. 19)
          - Identified large groups (Box 272)
            (folder no. 20)
          - Identified small groups (Box 272)
            (folder no. 21)
          - Unidentified individuals (Box 272)
            (folder no. 22)
          - Unidentified large groups (Box 272)
            (folder no. 23)
          - Unidentified small groups (Box 272)
            (folder no. 24)
      - Consumer concerns (Box 272)
        (folder no. 25)
      - Conventions (political) (Box 272)
        (folder no. 26)
      - Detroit riots, 1967 (Box 272)
        (folder no. 27)
      - Dirksen, Everett (Box 272)
        (folder no. 28)
      - Environment (includes Sleeping Bear Dunes and Pictured Rocks Lakeshores) (Box 272)
        (folder no. 29)
      - Family (Box 272)
        (folder no. 32)
      - Hart, Jane Briggs (Box 272)
        (folder no. 33)
      - Hart, Philip
        - Bearded, gesturing and at phone (Box 272)
          (folder no. 34)
        - Bearded, head and shoulders (Box 272)
          (folder no. 35)
        - Bearded, reading, writing (Box 272)
          (folder no. 36)
        - Without beard, formal and mug shots (Box 272)
          (folder no. 37)
          (SEE ALSO oversize folder, UAm)
        - Without beard, informal shots (Box 272)
          (folder no. 38)
        - Without beard, outdoor shots (Box 272)
          (folder no. 39)
        - Without beard, telephone and mike shots (Box 272)
          (folder no. 40)
      - Hearings (Box 272)
        (folder no. 41)
      - Honors received-academic (Box 272)
        (folder no. 42)
      - Honors received-banquet in Detroit (Edmund Muskie, speaker) (Box 272)
        (folder no. 43)
      - Honors received-other (Box 272)
        (folder no. 44)
      - Inaugurals (Box 272)
        (folder no. 45)
      - International (Box 272)
        (folder no. 46)
      - International-Poznan Fair, 1963 (Box 272)
        (folder no. 47)
      - Kennedy, Robert and Edward (Box 272)
        (folder no. 48)
      - Labor (Box 272)
        (folder no. 49)
      - Laboratory shots (Box 272)
        (folder no. 50)
      - McNeely, James-reception for, Washington, March 5, 1969 (Box 272)
        (folder no. 51)
      - Michigan-promotion (Box 272)
        (folder no. 52)
      - Michigan-Washington Conference of Community Officials, May 21, 1964 (Box 272)
        (folder no. 53)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 272)
        (folder no. 54)
      - Office shots (Box 272)
        (folder no. 55)
      - Peace movement (Box 272)
        (folder no. 56)
      - Philippines trip (Box 272)
        (folder no. 57)
      - Poverty and Resurrection City (Washington D.C., 1968) (Box 272)
        (folder no. 58)
      - Presidents